# Jennifer Pierre



**Graphic Designer** Web Design

285 rue Woodland, apt.3 Verdun, Qc, Canada H4H 1V5



jennifer.bijou2386@gmail.com



My Porfolio



(514) 716-4402

linkedin.com/in/jenniferbijou

### About me

Hi, I'm Jennifer! I am investing into coding knowlege. I have been working as graphic designer for 4 years and I want to expend my knowledge of web developpement.

I seek to continue my knowledge of front-end and graphic design in order to meet the needs and wishes of my clients, who expect from me much more than creative talent.

LANGUAGES

#### **EXPERIENCES**

Aug. 2016 - March 2021 Axis Lighting - Graphic Designer and Client Support; Marketing Department

**Graphic Designer:** 

Worked on the Front-End and Back-End in both company websites;

Make the brochures and flyers and create a french version,

giving by our tranalator;

Create stationnary, poster and other for the company; Create logos and icons for the specification sheets.

Client Support:

Create Marketing sales orders for customer demand;

Prepare the room for each clients visits;

Help HR to order and prepare giveaways for the annual ski trip;

Marketing:

Take care of Marketing giveaways;

Prepare the Marketing's luminaire sample for sales orders; Arrange the sample of luminaires in Mezz and Productions.

March 2015 Stage (Masoda Media)

Start a project given by the project manager;

Feb. 2015 - Oct. 2017

Create and make scarves with the client on Photoshop and Illustrator.

January 2015 Cloé & cie

Redraw their mascot on Illustrator.

July 2007 - Aug. 2016 Globo Chaussures - 3rd key position (Team leader)

Cashier, serving and helping customers;

Prepare the visual presentation in the Kids and Athletics section;

Ensure the cleanliness of the store.

March 2006 - July 2006 Domino's Pizza - Cashier and receptionist

Place orders and answer the phone;

Keep the restaurant and the kitchen section clean.

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 Udemy - online course (in progress)

Web Design Bootcamp (Certificated of Completion)

Août 2015 Collège CDI

Graphic Design (AEC)

2013 Cégep du Vieux Montréal

Accueil et d'intégration

Sciences humaines - Profil Individu Regards sur la personne

## **SKILLS**



Photoshop









WordPress











JavaScript



#### QUALITIES

Jovial, trustworthy and likes to learn Ambitious and able to work in a team Effective in problem solving Punctual and Meticulous Curious and love to help others



Able to work with PCs and Macs





**INTERESTS** 











